How's it going?
Hey, how's it going?
I'm actually a fan.
I see you a lot.
I'm Pierce Morgan.
Okay, thank you for watching.
Yeah.
So my argument is that Americans are, what is a nation?
A nation is a geographical location full of people who have some things in common.
So I think some of the things, typically in history, are going to be like race, religion,
ethnicity, language.
These are some of the things that we have to have in common in order to actually have
a functioning civilization, especially in self-government.
I'm not necessarily a giant fan of self-government.
I'm a Catholic nationalist.
I'm not a fascist.
You have to have at least some things in common in order to actually have a civilization.
And the immigrants, especially illegal immigrants that come into this country now, disrespect
us.
They hate everything that we believe.
They don't even speak our language.
I watched, after Trump got elected, I watched an interview of an illegal alien woman crying
about getting deported.
And the entire interview was in Spanish.
That is a spit in the face.
It's disrespect.
They don't care about us.
They abuse our system.
So you've gone from a teleological argument into just a bunch of series of wild, unsubstantiated
claims.
Well, I'm asking you, what is the claim?
I don't accept any of those claims.
OK.
What's the point of a country?
That they hate everything we stand for.
And I don't accept...
Well, I'm not going to deal with the teleology.
I'm going to deal with the false claims that you made.
OK.
Go ahead.
There's no...
What's your basis for saying that all immigrants or all undocumented immigrants hate everything
we stand for?
It's funny that you said you're a Catholic nationalist.
How did most Catholics get to America?
Irish Catholics, Italian Catholics, immigration.
How much of the people coming across the southern border are Catholics?
Yeah, I know.
I don't...
So it's really funny that you say you're a Catholic nationalist, but Catholics came to
America via immigration.
Yeah.
So there's...
So immigration is good for America.
You and I can agree.
Otherwise, people of your faith wouldn't be here.
No.
Well, we were here on this side of the world, in this continent from conquest.
We came over here and...
But the big surges of numbers, as you well know, because you're a smart guy, Italian,
Irish immigration waves, Catholic immigration waves.
OK, yeah.
And I'm not even claiming...
Well, I'm not even claiming that immigration is bad.
Because a lot of people are against those.
I'm not claiming immigration is bad in all cases, at all times.
What is your claim?
My claim is that immigration, especially now, and especially for foreign people that have
nothing in common with us, is a negative thing.
It's funny that you say it's especially now.
I forgot your name.
My apologies.
Brian.
Yeah.
How many...
In every era, there has been a Brian who says, I'm not against immigration, just immigration
now.
OK.
This is what people said about Italians.
It's what people said about Irish folks.
That's unfortunate.
Said about Russians, Poles.
And now we're saying about people coming across the southern border.
Because you're not being...
You're being a little disingenuous saying, I'm only against immigrants now.
This is a trope.
How is that disingenuous?
Because it's a trope that's been used by nativists throughout American history.
And every wave of immigrants has come in and faced the same hate and animus and bigotry
and lazy trope.
And every wave of immigration has ultimately assimilated, integrated, benefited the country.
In fact, assimilation right now, according to Jacob Vigdor from the University of Washington,
assimilation rates based on language and citizenship and naturalization are higher now than 100
years ago.
OK, let me make a statement first.
You ignored my statement.
You and your own person are a complete, perfect example of why immigration is negative and
why we shouldn't allow people who don't have anything in common with us.
You're pro-abortion.
You're pro-euthanasia.
You're pro...
I'm pro-euthanasia?
Yeah, you went...
I've seen your stuff.
You've defended euthanasia.
I'm pro-euthanasia?
Yeah.
On Piers Morgan.
No, I've never discussed euthanasia with Piers Morgan in my life.
OK, so my point is that you don't agree with the founders of this country.
If anyone watching at home, I'm the only guy here who actually supports American values,
democracy, free speech, the Constitution.
I've got folks here telling me they don't believe in democracy, that they're nationalists.
Wait, why should we care about that, by the way?
Isn't that what America stands for?
What does America stand for?
No, why?
So you hate what America stands for, not me.
No, I'm not even saying...
And in fact, all the studies show that immigrants actually are more patriotic than native-born
Americans.
So the only reason...
The only reason why...
Yeah, that's the Mexicans in L.A. right now burning it down, waving Mexican flags.
L.A.'s being burned down?
Please don't send us back to the country that we're waving the flag of.
I've been in L.A. for a few days.
I didn't see anything burned down.
Yeah, I know.
The riots have ended.
That's because Trump sent...
But if it's burned down, where's it all burned down?
I haven't seen it.
They firebombed cars.
They firebombed Waymo.
You said L.A. was burned down.
L.A.'s 500 square miles.
It's not a figure of speech.
I'm just another false claim of yours.
I'm saying that they're burning...
No, no, no.
They're burning buildings.
I support euthanasia.
L.A.'s burned to the ground.
No, no, no.
Bro, just listen.
Relax.
Immigrants hate what we stand for.
I'm super relaxed.
And I'm standing by my position.
Immigrants are a good thing.
You're pro-abortion.
You're an immigrant.
I'm pro-Roe v. Wade.
Personally, I'm not pro-abortion.
If you knew anything about me, you'd know.
Yeah, Roe v. Wade is...